export const questionaire = [
  {
    question_no: 0,
    question: "Props are __________ into other components",
    options: {
      a: "Injected",
      b: "Methods",
      c: "Both A and B",
      d: "All of the these",
    },
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question_no: 1,
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    options: {
      a: "Server-side framework",
      b: "User-interface framework",
      c: "Both",
      d: "None",
    },
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question_no: 2,
    question:
      "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    options: {
      a: "Original DOM",
      b: "Virtual DOM",
      c: "Both  A and B",
      d: "None of the above.",
    },
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question_no: 3,
    question: "What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
    options: {
      a: "3000",
      b: "8000",
      c: "8080",
      d: "3030",
    },
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question_no: 4,
    question: "What is a state in React?",
    options: {
      a: "A permanent storage.",
      b: "Internal storage of the component.",
      c: "External storage of the component.",
      d: "None of the above.",
    },
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question_no: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following option is correct in the case of the Babel??",
    options: {
      a: "Babel is a Compiler.",
      b: "Babel is a Transpiler",
      c: "None of the above.",
      d: "Both A and B are correct.",
    },
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    question_no: 6,
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    options: {
      a: "Server-side framework",
      b: "User-interface framework",
      c: "Both",
      d: "None",
    },
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question_no: 7,
    question: "Props are __________ into other components",
    options: {
      a: "Injected",
      b: "Methods",
      c: "Both A and B",
      d: "All of the these",
    },
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question_no: 8,
    question:
      "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    options: {
      a: "Original DOM",
      b: "Virtual DOM",
      c: "Both  A and B",
      d: "None of the above.",
    },
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question_no: 9,
    question: "What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
    options: {
      a: "3000",
      b: "8000",
      c: "8080",
      d: "3030",
    },
    answer: "c",
  },
  //   {
  //     question_no: 10,
  //     question: "What is a state in React?",
  //     options: {
  //       a: "A permanent storage.",
  //       b: "Internal storage of the component.",
  //       c: "External storage of the component.",
  //       d: "None of the above.",
  //     },
  //     answer: "b",
  //   }
];
